I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from? From
Я из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда Из
Belgrade
белграда
itself is Belgorod Well, yes, yes, a badge-fly I’ve already
само Белгорода Ну да да бляха-муха Я уже
forgotten, to be honest, that there is Belgorod
и забыл честно говоря что есть Белгород
before, how were they so happy about the shelling of
раньше как это так радовались обстрелам
Belgorod, some Shebekinos have now already
Белгорода какие-то Шебекино сейчас уже
forgotten about them, Sevastopol is [ __ ]
забыли про них уже Севастополь ебашит
just in full swing there are shellings of
просто полным ходом есть обстрелы
Belgorod  region now
Белгородской области сейчас
Well, I can’t hear anymore We’re just giving I
Ну я не слышу уже Мы просто даем я вот
understand
понял
regularly every day and I even forgot
регулярно каждый день и уже даже забыл
before I was so happy Now
раньше так радовался Теперь же
Sevastopol, damn it, they brought yesterday’s
Севастополь блин такой привели вчерашний
arrival in Sevastopol at the
прилет по севастополю по штабу
Nazi headquarters, so many were killed there by a
нацистов столько убили там
British missile like the Russian ones, these
британская ракета типа российских этих
generals like fleet admirals, in short, the
генералов типа адмиралов флота короче
chief  I
начальника этих всех
don’t know any reason to be happy about all of them, damn it’s
не знаю вообще повода радоваться [__]
that people are being killed honestly, they’re
то что людей убивают его честно
killing us. Well, look, if these
они Нас убивают Ну а что смотри если эти
dudes aren’t people. They came to kill us
чуваки не люди Они нас пришли убивать то
when they were liquidated. That’s cool. Well, we
когда их ликвидировали Это же круто Ну
survived, it’s cool, and I’m telling you,
мы сохранились круто да я тебе говорю за
no one stands for civilians.  suffered no one suffered the
никто не пострадал никто не пострадал
Black Sea Fleet
Черноморском флота
for Belgorod
за Белгород
Putin will be judged for will be judged this way
Путина будет судить за будут судить так
because you have why they are suffering
потому что у вас из-за чего они страдают
because where are your military people hiding?
потому что военные где прячутся ваши
So they would go out into an open field and
Вот они взяли бы вышли в чистое поле и
say like in an open field they are bastards you
сказали типа в чистом поле они [__]
see in the cities  Do
видите в городах
you have a military unit in Belgorod?
есть у вас воинская часть в Белгороде
No idea. Therefore, keep
Без понятия Поэтому смотри
everyone in Belgorod peaceful. Try not to
мирным всем Белгороде Старайтесь не
be near military installations near
находиться возле военных объектов возле
administrative buildings and it’s better to
административные зданий и лучше вообще
leave the territory of the Belgorod region altogether.
покиньте территории Белгородской области
What is your name Androniy
Как зовут тебя андроний
Androni crack I have a Greek name that you don’t
андронь кряк я греческое имя что ты не
like Okay okay Listen, look
нравится Ладно хорошо Слушай вот смотри
Like if  I’m speaking for something else. That is, I’m here
Типа если говорю За другое То есть я вот
where the explosions don’t reach me.
нахожусь где до меня взрывы не доходит
It happens that an arrival there, something was shot
бывает что прилет там что-то сбили там я
down there, I don’t know. That is, fragments fall there, that
не знаю То есть осколки там падает то
is, look, I’ll just tell you
есть вот смотрите просто расскажу
the situation, if you’re interested, you can listen
ситуацию если интересно можешь послушать
and if not, you can switch. Interesting I’ll
и нет можешь переключиться Интересно
tell you the situation where  I was working
Расскажу ситуацию где работал
at the same time. Well, I was working on
одновременно Ну я мочка машин работал
cars, and I was working on cars, and it turns out that literally across
машины был и получается буквально через
the road, well, just a [ __ ] stone’s throw away, there was a
дорогу ну [__] рукой подать сидел
little child sitting, these really, well, this is not a
маленький ребенок эти реально ну это не
fairy tale. I’m telling you seriously, and the
сказку Я тебе серьезно говорю и пошли
parents went to the store and it’s like, just
родители в магазин и типа просто вот
such a dumbass flew the [ __ ] into the
такая вот залупа прилетела нахуй в
car. Where the child got scared  [ __ ] up, you
машину Где ребенок перепугался [__] ты
think it’s normal, normal children
считаешь нормально нормально дети
Yes, because I don’t understand, I’m explaining
Да потому что я не понимаю я объясняю
because the authorities should have
потому что власть должна была
evacuated if there was something
эвакуировать если там э близко к зоне
going on there close to the combat zone, and the authorities of the
боевых действий что идут и власти
Belgorod region should have
Белгородской области должны были
announced an evacuation and taken the civilian
объявить эвакуацию и забрать мирных
population somewhere, damn it, to Moscow, for example,
населения куда-то блин в Москву например
to sit  to the boarding house Why you have an
посидеть в пансионат Почему у вас
announced evacuation I do
объявленная эвакуация
n’t know, I just look how much if
не знаю я так вот смотри сколько если
the governor knows that shelling is going on
губернатор знает что идут обстрелы
every day Why don’t they evacuate the civilian
каждый день Почему не эвакуируют мирное
population, they took away the civilian population,
население забрали мирное население
they put only the military And the
ставили только военных И всё не
little boy wouldn’t have suffered, damn it, that’s
пострадал бы маленький мальчик блин вот
how you really reason like that
так на самом деле ты так рассуждаешь так
like everything you say is so simple It’s just, well,
типа всё у тебя на словах так Всё просто
so simple
ну так просто
And look, they’re evacuating a
А смотри эвакуируют
special one You started a special
специальную Вы же начали специально
military operation here The
военную операцию у вас Суть в другой
point is different, look if you care, at least
смотри если вы какая разница хоть туда
look there I’ll explain to you, think with your own
смотри Объясняю тебе подумай своей
head if you have Belgorodskaya, look
головой если у вас Белгородская смотри
Until the twenty-fourth of February 22  year
До двадцать четвёртого февраля 22 года у
you had at least one increase was an urban
вас был хоть один прирост был городской
area. I had no idea, so if
области Без понятия не было так вот если
Putin is conducting a special military
Путин проводит специальную военную
operation, then in the house of a
операцию да то в доме проведения
special operation. He must protect the
специальной операции Он должен защитить
population from the healer. If
население от целитель Если пригоняют
your authorities bring them in. Yes, they bring them to Belgorodskaya,
ваши власти Да пригоняют в Белгородскую
you have a bunch of military personnel, so I’m forming there
у вас кучу военных так формирую там
divisions that shell Kharkov and
дивизионы которые обстреливают Харьков и
so on, and then they have to take the population from there, they
так дальше да то должны забрать оттуда
take it,
население они берут
declare a special military operation,
объявляют специальную военную операцию
bring troops to Belgorod,
военную приводят в Белгород войска
Belgorod region,
Белгородскую область
place them like this among the civilian
расставляют их вот так между мирного
population, and then they are surprised what
населения Да и потом удивляются что
happens because this is a war
случается потому что это военное
crime, the Moscow regime cannot
преступление Московского режима нельзя
carry out a special military  a military
проводить военную специальную военную
operation in a certain territory without
операцию в определенной территории не
evacuating the civilian population from there
эвакуировав оттуда мирное население
when the police, for example, carry out some kind of
когда полиция например проводят какие-то
anti-terrorist
антитеррористические
measures What do people do, they take
мероприятия Что делают людей выводят
the publication out if, for example, there is some kind of terrorist
издание если например террорист какой-то
in the building or a bomb is planted, the first
в здании есть или бомба заложена первым
thing they do is take people out of the building, the
делом людей выводят из здания приходит
evacuation of
эвакуация
those in the buildings occurs When a special operation is carried out  a
находящихся в зданий Когда проводится
military operation
специальная военная операция
is carrying out the evacuation of the population from the
проводится эвакуация населения с
territory in which a
территории на которой проводится
special military operation is being carried out if
специальная военная операция если
Putin's Moscow regime decided
путинский Московский режим решил
to conduct a special military operation to
провести специальную военную операцию по
protect the Donbass dynastication of the
защите Донбасса династификации
demilitarization of Ukraine, he should
демилитаризации Украины он должен в
first of all
первую очередь был своих конституционных
ensure the safety of
землях обеспечить безопасность
his own population on his constitutional lands
собственного населения
by announcing
путем объявления
[music]
[музыка]
evacuation of the population, but this  not done
эвакуации населения но это не сделано
because of the carelessness of your leadership
из-за безалаберности вашего руководства
and the fact that it considers you [ __ ]
и того что она вас считает говном с
that can be ignored Putin still
которым можно не считаться Путину все
has an avenue of angels in Belgorod
равно есть у вас аллея ангелов Белгороде
How many children have already died
Сколько уже детей погибло
there has been a year and a half
есть полтора года
it has dominated
это доминировала
That is, in short, damn it, the faces of the earth have been erased
То есть то что короче блин стерлись лица
Mariupol is not his  it’s surprising that his
Мариуполь его не удивляет то что его
Belgorod region is ironed by Kharkov Yes, and a
Белгородской области утюжат Харьков Да и
soldier so that a bunch of people from Kharkov are
солдатку чтобы куча людей из Харькова
forced to live in other cities he
вынуждены жить в других городах он
Khmelnitsky a bunch of Kharkovites in Poland a
Хмельницком куча харьковчанда в Польше
bunch of Kharkovites all over the world a bunch
куча харьковчан по всему миру куча
of Kharkovites Yes, this doesn’t surprise him, but the fact
харьковчан Да это его не удивляет а то
that something flew there the answer is
что что-то прилетело там ответ
six by us  kilogram right at a time autumn and
шесть нами килограмм прям за раз осень а
experience
опыт
[music]
[музыка]
driving us through quarries into a shadow ban
загоняя нас через карьерки в теневый бан
and even then the video is not shown to people
и дуже то видео не показывается людям
information about streams is often shown
часто показывается информация про стримы
in order to have a little operational whistle
для того чтобы мало оперативный свисток
right at a time and butt there video
прям за раз а попок там видео
[music]
[музыка]